Koichi?
I'm over here, Koichi.
Rohan Kishibe!
Now, now, you don't
have to be so defensive.
My days of causing you harm
are long past. Besides,
after reading your history
with Heaven's Door,
I found myself filled with a
deep sense of respect for you.
I'd go so far as to say
we're two peas in a pod.
Wouldn't you agree?
now then i'd like to ask
you a question if i may
you see i used to call
this area around here my
home until i was four
or so i've spent the day
trying to find my old
residence nostalgia must have
gotten the better of me
recalling one's childhood
is central to a manga
artist's work however those
memories belong to a
four-year-old so they're
a little bit foggy oh that's
why i I need your help.
My question concerns this town map.
There's something odd about it.
Look, this is the Soba Shop, Ariskawa,
Caesar Drugstore, and the
Ocean Convenience Store.
They're situated right to left.
Now, take a look at the shops themselves.
From the right, you can see Ariskawa,
Caesar Drugstore, and then...
You have Ocean on the far
left. See? Huh? That's weird.
The map doesn't show a road
between Ocean and the drugstore.
What sloppy work?
Koichi, would you tag along?
I would be forever in your debt if
you'd be my guide for a bit. Huh?
Well, I'd like to, but the thing is...
That's the response you give
after I ask so politely?
Fine, have it your way.
I didn't realize showing me around for
a few meters would be such a burden.
He sure is self-centered.
I can only spare five
minutes, okay, Sensei?
Strange, isn't it?
I'm checking my official Chan
press ultra-detailed map of Mariah,
and it makes no mention
of this street existing.
On the bright side, since
your map had an error,
you might get a gift
certificate at the bookstore.
Blast it, this map is absolutely useless.
Take a look, Koichi.
It doesn't show the Yonimori,
Honma, or Onodera residence.
There are mistakes everywhere.
The bookstore is going to owe me more
than two or three gift certificates.
Rohan-sensei, this place looks
like it's been abandoned.
What a weird area.
The few houses that are around
here look completely unoccupied.
And look, even the vending
machines are out of order.
What the?
It's the mailbox.
We made our first turn at this corner
when we came down the alleyway.
This is too weird.
Somehow we've managed to end
up right back where we started.
But we turned right, left, then right.
Keep your guard up.
There could be an enemy nearby,
manipulating things with their stand.
You think?
If you would, have Reverb fly
overhead and search the area.
Yeah, of course.
From up there, I can
see where we need to go.
Reverb, act one.
What's the matter?
There was something up there.
I don't know what, but
something just graced Reverb.
Are you sure?
I didn't see anything.
I know something came
into contact with Reverb.
Excuse me, are you too lost?
I would be happy to be your guide.
A girl?
She must be the enemy stand user!
Heaven's door!
And with a flick of a
finger, victory is mine!
We should be safe now.
I've written commands in her pages,
so she won't be able to harm us.
Sensei, that was amazing!
It's like you launched
your drawing into midair!
I've made quite a lot of
progress with my stand.
That said,
it still doesn't work on
haters like Josuke who
wouldn't know art if it
kicked him in the groin.
She and I are on the same wavelength.
Oh, dear.
She's just an ordinary
girl, not an enemy. Huh?
So she's not out to get us?
That's right.
You can't conceal anything
from heaven's door.
Her name is Reimi Sugimoto, age 16.
Her address is 312 Code Daimorio.
That's not far from here.
She has no boyfriend and her measurements
are 82, 57, and 84 centimeters.
There's a mole by her left nipple, and her
first period came at age 11 in September.
The first time she kissed a boy, he
rammed his tongue down her throat.
That's just about enough, Rohan!
If this girl's not a stand user,
then I refuse to allow you to
read anything else about her life!
All right, all right, I get it.
Take it easy.
I will forget everything that
has just happened. There.
I'd be happy to guide you.
Really, this place trips
a lot of people up.
Several of these alleys look the same.
Please point us in the right
direction and we'll be on our way.
Absolutely not.
A simple explanation won't cut it.
I'm your guide, so follow me.
Want one?
If you're sure, but you still
have to hold on to the end.
Uh-oh!
Better be careful.
Some girl is gonna dump you.
Really?
Where's your proof?
Poco fortune-telling.
The break tells me all about you.
You're majorly self-centered,
and you have a habit of pushing
people's buttons, don't you?
That's why you're going to get dumped.
Get a load of this, Koichi.
Now we know she's off her rocker.
She actually thinks I'm self-centered.
You're about to find out
two can play at this game.
Light pink nail polish
means you're afraid of love.
That's very telling.
You often let love slip
through your fingers.
No way.
I use psychological prodding over
fortune-telling, but enough about your love life.
Something else is weighing on your mind
Have you heard the story about this house?
It said it was the scene of a murder
15 years ago Did she say a murder?
Yes, she did
No one lives in the house now.
It's empty. Here's why.
This story was told to me
by the old lady next door.
It happened in the dead of night,
while the young girl was
sleeping soundly in her bedroom.
She awoke to a strange dripping sound that
seemed to be emanating
from her parents' room,
but she couldn't be sure.
The sound puzzled her. Daddy! Mommy!
she called out, but she
never heard a reply.
However,
the girl wasn't particularly scared, because
she was accompanied by her trusty dog.
Her dog?
Yes, he was a big guard dog.
In the darkness, she'd offer
her hand to him under the bed,
and he'd always respond
with a whimper and a lick.
Arnold was her constant reassurance.
But the dripping that
had stolen the girl from
her peaceful slumber
continued for several minutes.
Finally she'd had enough her curiosity
drove her to investigate what happened next.
She found arnold with his throat slashed
hanging from the coat
rack like an old pelt.
The dripping sound was
coming from him the sound
of his spilling blood
suddenly she heard a voice.
Coming from under her bed your hand is so
sweet and tender
sweetheart whimper whimper.
I've already murdered
your mommy and daddy.
And then he attacked the girl,
killing her when she died!
Tell me that story was just
your way of joking around!
Sounded pretty real, didn't it?
You babies, that's for
the nail polish crack.
Jeez, my heart can't take stuff like that.
That means...
Yes, the young girl in
the story was yours truly.
Arnold and I only exist as ghosts.
They're ghosts?
It all makes sense now.
Heaven's door could only
access her living memories.
This has never happened to me before.
The two of you have stumbled upon the
area where I met my end 15 years ago.
I guess we're on the same wavelength.
This place is the gateway
between the living and the dead.
Come on, Koichi, run!
Huh?
Damn, we're stuck.
Keicho, call Reverb.
It can give us directions from above.
She must have been the one who
made contact with Reverb earlier.
Never mind that. Just do it!
What?
A wall appeared in the sky.
No, that's not it.
Reverb's actually touching the ground.
Huh?
What in the?
I can't believe this, but
you're the one who's floating.
There's only one way to truly escape.
Anything else is futile.
I'm the only one who knows where it is.
This doesn't make any sense.
How the hell do we fight a ghost?
Please, whatever you do, don't possess us!
Hold on just a minute.
Quit treating me like a vengeful spirit.
I haven't done a single
thing to either of you,
but somehow you've found a way to
scare yourselves half to death.
Listen, I didn't trap you guys here.
We're standing between the living
world and the world of the dead.
Wait a second.
You two hold some kind of power, right?
And you said they're called stands?
Maybe that's why you're
mixed up in all this.
So you're really not here to attack us?
You're even more
suspicious than I thought.
I guess I'm proof of
that stone tape theory.
Once I became a ghost, I
was bound to this place.
I've been here 15 years.
In all that time, I've never stopped
pleading with people to listen.
To let me share my story.
But you two are the first
to have truly listened.
I gave you my word I'd help you get out
of here, so that's what I'm going to do.
But after I finish the story...
There's more?
Now, as I was saying, the murderer.
Before I got a look at his face, his
knife found its way into my back.
It was late and dark, and I
was doing my best to flee.
I died, but my killer still lives.
He's living his life right here in Mariah.
That's what I've been aching to say.
Not only is he in town, he's blended in!
Let's back this specter train up.
Why are you confessing all this to us?
Relax, I'm not asking you to catch him.
I just need you to tell someone who will.
You can tell the cops or anybody
else you think is up to the task.
Slow down!
Why the hell should that kind of
responsibility fall on our shoulders?
Rohan-sensei!
Compose yourself I think it's
best we remain level-headed
It's an absolute tragedy I'm sorry
your life was stolen from you,
but that still doesn't explain things.
We find the murderers
so you can get closure?
That all seems rather
pointless, doesn't it?
You'd be better off
letting go of this world.
Surely moving on to the
next world would be a
better existence than
haunting these alleyways.
Tell me,
do you have any idea
how many innocent boys
and girls have gone
missing from this town? No.
Then you should know it's eight
times the national average.
Yes, and it gets even worse.
Some are being slaughtered in silence.
And he's behind it all.
Wait a minute!
You can't be serious!
This is still going on and
no one's done anything?!
Hey, you can't just say things like that!
According to this story, you
didn't even see his face!
How would you know what's going on?!
I know because I see the souls of
his victims dominating the skies!
It's as clear as day!
The wounds of those souls
are the same as mine!
It's horrifying.
That gash is so deep.
I can't speak with those
traveling to the other side,
but I see them depart over and over.
He's fueled by a twisted
obsession, one I know all too well.
Mariah has always been my
home, and for fifteen years,
it stood in the shadow of murder.
It's terrifying, and on a personal
level, it's utterly humiliating.
When they finally detain that wild animal,
my cherished Mariah will
have a new reputation.
all of Japan will know it
as the home of a monster.
But none of that changes the fact that
we have to stop him as fast as possible.
He's preying on someone as we speak.
And there's nothing at all I can do?
whose life will be ripped
away from them next.
You still have blood
pumping through your veins.
If you won't take back
Morio's peace and dignity,
then tell me who will and I'll
ask for their help instead.
I really hope you've taken
what I've said to heart.
I've nothing more to say.
Well, I heard you loud and clear, and
I'm shocked no one knows about this.
There has to be something we can do here!
How altruistic, Koichi.
This smells like treble.
Although, this vicious killer could
be a good source of inspiration.
It all seems like it'd make
for some interesting manga.
Can we get out if we go this way?
Don't buy the good guy act.
It's obvious that he has ulterior motives.
And when it comes to trustworthiness,
the guy's shady at best.
Did you hear a word I just said?
Then we're agreed.
I'll show you how to get to the exit.
Huh? The exit?
Where do we find it?
If you go past the mailbox,
you'll find it on the left.
Yeah!
Hey, slow down!
Trust me, you don't want to rush it.
There's a rule to making it through.
There's a rule?
Yes.
Once you make it past the mailbox,
you'll see the exit about 20 meters away.
No matter what happens around that corner,
I need you both to promise me
you'll never look behind you.
Why not?
What would be there?
That's just the rule for
passing to the next world.
Even Arnold understands
something as simple as that.
Okay, if a dog can handle it, I guess
there's no reason I wouldn't be able to.
And if we do look back, what happens then?
Well, putting it in layman's terms, your
souls would be dragged into the next world.
Put bluntly, you would die.
But don't worry.
It'll be a piece of cake.
All you have to do is look forward.
Simple, right?
Did you feel something, Koichi?
Yeah, when we passed the mailbox, something
flew past our legs and went behind us!
Remember, eyes front!
Just stay calm and you'll be fine.
You feel that, Rohan-sensei?
There's some kind of ominous
presence creeping up behind us!
Yes, I'm aware.
Something's there I don't know what
but there's something right by my head.
Just ignore it there will always be
something trying to make you look back.
I know it seems scary
and overwhelming but as
long as you don't look
back it can't do anything.
To cause you harm there's
something warm and
runny oozing down my neck
ignoring this thing's.
Gonna be a lot tougher
than you're making it
sound almost there go
through the light and.
You're home free.
What?
But I can't take any more of this.
And it's so far away.
Let's run for it, Rohan sensei.
Panicking will make it worse.
It'll try to trip you.
You're safe now.
You made it.
You can turn around now. Go ahead.
I've never been so terrified.
Thank goodness it's all.
No, that wasn't me.
Don't look back.
It's trying to get you to turn around.
You idiot.
Koichi, if only you had waited for us.
But this didn't happen when I
came through here by myself.
Why'd they trick him?
Koichi, no!
I don't get it, but if we don't
look, we're good to go, right?
You lucked out, Koichi.
You're with me.
Heaven's door!
I'm taking your ability to see.
You're welcome.
You can calm down, Koichi.
I'll reinscribe your ability to see.
The alley between the convenience
store and the drugstore.
It disappeared.
I'm just glad we're back.
I'm afraid this is as far as we go.
Well, at least until he's caught.
When that finally happens,
Arnold and I will look back, and
we'll be reunited with Mom and Dad.
Peace and dignity must return to Morioh.
Only then can we find eternal rest.
I'll be right here if you ever
want to talk about anything.
You two don't be strangers, okay?
I'm here if you need me,
little Rohan, Mr. Koichi.
From the bottom of my heart, I want to
thank you for listening to my story.
She had some nerve.
Where does she get off
calling me little Rohan?
What an audacious ghost girl.
But still, Reimi Sugimoto.
She has an unyielding spirit, and
that's something to be respected.
For 15 years,
she's waged a fight for the living with
nothing but her courage
and trusted companion.
There it is, Reimi, age 16.
I never doubted her story, but
it's nice to have evidence.
Ah, we have a visitor.
You wouldn't happen to be Rohan
Kishibe, the manga artist, would you?
Sorry, have we met before?
Let's see.
I'd say you would have been
about four when it happened.
It doesn't surprise me you have
no recollection of that night.
So, I'll start by saying your
house was close to theirs.
The night of the incident your
parents left home for the evening,
apparently there was some urgent
business that needed attention.
Your parents and the Sugimoto's
were very close friends,
so they left you with them while
they handled matters elsewhere.
Rohan, that night, the one that claimed
the lives of the Sugimoto family,
you were there and the only one rescued.
I was... there?
You were able to survive that nightmare?
But once you were in police custody, you
started crying and repeating this sentence.
Big Sis Reimi snuck me out
the window and saved me.
Reimi risked everything to get you to
safety before the murderer could find you.
Now it all makes sense.
No wonder she acted so familiar.
And I learned something
else, my heaven's door.
It can't reveal my distant
memories or personal fate.
If you ever find yourself wandering
down this alleyway, a word of warning,
you should never, ever look back.
I'm telling you, I really met a ghost!
The girl you saw in that
picture is me dreamy!
I already said that we believe you.
Right, Okuyasu?
This Code is just my type.
If only I'd been born 15 years earlier.
If she's gonna stick around, we should
probably meet your ghost friend too.
But fair warning, Koichi.
If we go to Jotaro or Mr.
Joseph about all this, you can bet your
ass they'll have one question for you.
This unknown killer.
Is he using a stand on his victims?
Uh, I guess.
I really don't know.
Well, in that case, it's up
to the police and courts.
What are you saying?
There's a bloodthirsty
murderer loose in Morioh!
Yeah, I know that.
And I'm telling you that Jotaro
and the Speedwagon Foundation
aren't going after an ordinary
killer no matter how twisted he is.
Now take a deep breath.
He's managed to avoid
the police for over a
decade and they're
supposed to be the best.
It's not like we're
going to summon him like
waving down some taxi
by force of will alone.
Let's stay calm and take
things slowly and carefully.
So, what did ol' Rohan have to say?
He said the same thing as
you, Josuke Be careful,
Koichi You have to be alert
when you cross the road
I'm sorry for the trouble
Mariah used to be a summer
escape for samurai I know,
such an out-there concept might be hard to
believe But my ancestors were among them.
We were ruined during
my grandfather's time.
All I have left is the house
that I currently live in.
Oh, and my miserable little office job.
Hey, what happened to that nice
imported watch I bought you?
That's right.
You left it in your bag.
How could I forget?
If I remember correctly,
I was loose on you.
We'll fix that tomorrow.
Hmm?
What's wrong?
Why are you being coy all of a sudden?
Now, watch your step as you get out.
Let's head inside.
A sublime weekend is beyond those doors.
It'll be our getaway.
Look at this, you're tripping.
Not at all becoming of a lady.
I expect you to clean this up.
I can't recall your name, but
in the long run does it matter.
And brava, it's all clean.
You should be proud of yourself.
Now then...
I think we should make some dinner.
What's the best dish in your repertoire?